geeks.com 2003-06-06

# Computer Geeks-About Us

* * *

About ComputerGeeks.com 

* * *

**Who we are and what we do:**

**ComputerGeeks.com** , headquartered in Oceanside, CA, is a leading direct-to-consumer e-commerce site specializing in providing computer-related excess inventory, manufacturer-closeouts, and high-demand computer components and peripherals at highly-discounted prices to tech-savvy, "Geeky", consumers-- you know who you are!

For more information, contact **ComputerGeeks.com:**

        1890 Ord Way  
        Oceanside, CA 92056  
        760.726.7700 tel  
        760.726.7723 fax  
        760.726.7759 technical support and returns

OR, [send us Email.](https://www.compgeeks.com/contactus.asp)

**ComputerGeeks.com** is entering its sixth year of online operation, and ships over 1,000 individual orders each business day. We own and warehouse all of our inventory-- all products visible on our site are **in stock, ready to ship** ,  and **include a warranty**.

Our website is driven by a sophisticated inventory-management database engine that updates website content in real time.  This means that "what you see is what we've got" for sale at any given time.  Products become invisible and/or marked as "Out of Stock" as they sell out.  Products not listed on our site are not currently available for sale, but that can change at any time!

**ComputerGeeks.com** is your number one source for the hottest deals on the 'Net: 

Don't be a dork... **_Shop @ The Geeks!_**

  * **ComputerGeeks.com** is committed to offering tremendous savings on computer products, and hosting a Web site providing a depth of value-added content. Our aim is to amuse, inform, and entertain you \-- while providing amazing values -- and to push the envelope of interactive Web functionality and secure online shopping ease... (it never pays to aim low.) 

  * This site is your direct link on the Web to the **hottest** deals in the computer industry! We purchase manufacturer excess, overstock, and slightly obsolete inventories in HUGE quantities. This allows us to offer products to you at truly remarkable prices. In the past we operated strictly at the dealer and corporate levels, but we've gone retail, bringing you the benefits and value traditionally available only to large volume commercial buyers.

  * We are always glad to receive feedback from visitors -- the best way for us to meet your needs is to know specifically what you want, so please, [ drop us a line.](http://www.computergeeks.com/contactus.asp)

  * **Sales Policies:** All sales are final. Sales Tax will be charged to all California residents. All items carry a 90 day warranty unless otherwise noted. Returns of product, other than for exchange or replacement, are subject to a 15% return fee. Shipping fees and/or return shipping costs are Non-Refundable. No returns other than non-working product after 30 days of receipt will be honored. Should a replacement for a returned item not be available, a credit will be issued or the product will be substituted with one of same-or-better specifications. Credits expire 6 months after date of issue. All returned equipment must be issued a Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) number prior to return shipment. To be accepted, all returned products must be conspicuously labeled with the assigned RMA number and accompanied with a copy of the sales order or invoice. Customer must pack items being returned complete, with all manuals, cables, accessories, etc., as if they were new and working condition. Regardless of condition, products must be packaged appropriately so as not to incur physical damage during return shipping.  Failure to do so may invalidate both the RMA and the warranty. Unauthorized and/or unmarked returns will not be honored. Computer Geeks will not be responsible for incidental or consequential damages arising from the use of any product(s) that it sells. The Computer Geeks Discount Outlet reserves the right to refuse service to anyone.

**Privacy Policies:** (Last Update: 2 October 2001)

**INTRODUCTION**

Computer Geeks is committed to protecting the privacy of our Visitors and Customers. Our privacy policy governs our use of private Visitor information and other information about our Visitors and Customers. Computer Geeks complies with the America Online (AOL) Certified Merchant privacy policy.

**Purpose**

Computer Geeks believes that our online 

**Visitors** and **Customers** need to be provided clear and prominent notice regarding what personal information is being collected about them, how it will be used, whether or not it will be disclosed, and if so, to whom.   

Many entities have examined the issue of privacy and developed guidelines for establishing reasonable policies. We believe that by addressing these issues, we will fulfill the goals of fair information use supported by the U.S. government and a variety of industry groups:[www.truste.org](http://www.truste.org/)  

**The Glossary of Terms** at the end of this Policy defines words with specific meaning as used in these guidelines.

**_Privacy Guidelines:_**

**Navigational Data/Tracking.**

We do not use any navigational data about where individuals come from, leave to, or go while on our Web site, and we do not disclose this to third parties.  
While we may collect online navigational data about where you go on our Web site, we will not use such information at the individually identifiable level. We may use navigational data in aggregate or compiled statistical form.   

We may use Web browser " **cookies**" to track progress through our Web site, but the cookies will not be used to collect or store individually identifiable information nor be linked to other information that allows us to identify an individual. However, we may use cookies with individual identifiers to support visitor enhancements such as AOL member authentication, site personalization, or eCommerce features (like your shopping cart.)  

**Information Sharing/Disclosure.**

We do not normally share navigational data with outside companies. If navigational information is shared, it is expressed only in aggregate or complied statistical form; we do not disclose individual names or personal navigational information.  

We do not disclose customer contact information (such as telephone numbers or various personal identification numbers), to any third party except as required by law, or as needed to fulfill an order or deliver a product that a customer has ordered.  

We do not disclose customer credit or debit card numbers or checking account information to any third party except as required by law, or as needed to fulfill an order or deliver a product that a customer has ordered.  

In support of maintaining a safe and secure environment for credit card purchases, it is essential to our customers that we use credit card and other billing account numbers only for the fulfillment of purchases or other transactions initiated by our Customers. We do not use credit card or other billing account numbers in other ways.   

We do not release to third parties specific customer account information except to comply with valid legal process or in reasonable efforts to fulfill a transaction initiated by our Customers.  

We provide Customers with the opportunity to update or correct contact and billing information.  
We provide to our customers a means to update and ensure the accuracy of their online contact and billing information. For security reasons, we will not disclose the original information directly to the customer, but rather provide a means to reenter changes to the information on record.   

**Online Purchases.**

The objective of the online purchases principle is to protect the information about customer transactions and other online uses from misuse and unauthorized disclosure.   

We may use information about the kinds of products you buy from us to make other marketing offers to you, unless you tell us not to, or to personalize your visits to our Web site. We do not give out this purchase data to others except as specified below:  

We do not give out information about what individual customers purchase, except to complete the transactions or to comply with valid legal process.   
However, pursuant to specific contracts, we may be required provide third-parties with listings of specific groups of customers who have made purchases. Generally, this data will be aggregated and not individually identifiable, but this may not be true in all cases.  

When we facilitate a transaction which is to be fulfilled by an outside party, we will not use the specific, individually identifiable transaction information collected from a customer for purposes other than fulfilling the transaction.

**Choice.**

We give you choices about how we use your personal information.  
The objective of the choice principle is to allow customers to opt-out of future marketing offers.

We give you choices about how the information that you provide may be used to make marketing offers to you. We provide you with a means to easily remove your contact information (like your email address) from marketing lists at any point in the future. Should you wish to be removed from our 100% opt-in Email subscribers list, [click here.](http://www.compgeeks.com/removeme.asp)

We do not sell or rent customer contact information to unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes.  

**Safeguarding Personal Information.**

The objective of the safeguarding personal information principle is to assure you that we actively protect your privacy using a variety of security and controls. We use secure technology, privacy protection controls and restrictions on employee access in order to safeguard your personal information.

We use state of the art technology (i.e., Secure Socket Layer, or SSL) encryption to keep customer personal information as secure as possible. We have also put in place privacy protection control systems designed to ensure that personal Customer data remains safe and private.  
To learn more about SSL data encryption and how it helps to secure you personal information, [click here.](http://addy.com/dc/html/what_is_ssl_.html)

We allow only authorized employees access to personal information and ensure that the access is limited by need.  

We require companies contracted as agents to adhere to confidentiality agreements to ensure that Customer information remains safe and secure.  

We require employees to acknowledge that they understand and will comply with our privacy policy. We subject employees who violate the privacy policy to disciplinary action.

**Safe Shopping Guarantee:   **We guarantee that every online transaction you make will be 100% safe.  Under the [**Fair Credit Billing Act**](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/credit/fcb.htm), your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

**Notice.**

We will keep you informed, clearly and prominently on this page, about what we do with your personal information, and we will advise you here if we change our policy. The objective of the notice principle is to ensure that you are aware of and understand how we protect your privacy.   

We explain to visitors and customers how their information is used by providing this written privacy policy for our visitors and customers.  

We notify customers of our privacy policy during registration when they make a purchase.  

We provide written notice of policy changes through prominent and ongoing disclosure.   

We provide a means for Visitors and Customers to ask questions about, voice concerns about, or report violations of the privacy policy. 

If you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, or to report a suspected violation of our privacy policy, you may contact us by the following means:

Email: 

OR 

Attn: Privacy  
ComputerGeeks.com  
1890 Ord Way  
Oceanside, CA 92056

**_GLOSSARY OF TERMS_**

**Account Information** : Information pertaining to and supporting the management of a customer's account, including but not limited to account numbers and other account identification, promotion information, registration/cancellation information, and preferences and profiles.  

**Aggregate** : Information considered as a whole or in groups. Compiled information that does not disclose individual identity.  

**Billing Information** : Customer generated information specific to a customer's billing and payment methods and history, including but not limited to bills, payment and billing statements, credit card number, credit card expiration date, checking account number, debit card number, and credit card type.  

**Choice** : Providing customers options about how their information can be used, such as opt-outs of email marketing offers.  

**Collection** : Requesting, recording, or generating information. The automatic or manual collection or receipt of customer information from a customer or other party.  

**Contact Information** : Information to support contacting customers, including but not limited to name, mailing address, telephone numbers, email addresses, and fax numbers.  

**Cookie**: A collection of data that gets entered into the memory of Web browsers by some Web sites. This data contains the domain, path, lifetime, and values of variables that are set by the Web site. Cookies may be "permanently" or temporarily stored as small text files on your computer's hard drive.  

**Customer**: Someone who has registered with us for the purpose of making a purchase or who has made a purchase from us in the past. Generally, we store much more information regarding Customers, including but not limited to Contact Information, Account Information, and Individually Identifiable Information. Customers are different from Visitors.  

**Disclosure** : The release of information to unafilliated third parties. Disclosure does not include release to those agents and vendors who are covered by appropriate non-disclosure and confidentiality agreements or release of information for the purpose of complying with valid legal process, to protect the rights or property of Computer Geeks, or for emergencies. If you initiate contact with a third party with regard to us, we may disclose your communication with us or other relevant informtion to that same third party.   

**Individually Identifiable Information** : Any information which can be used to identify a specific individual in particular by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to the individual's physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural status, or social affiliations.  

**Marketing** : Promotions provided by us. May be through direct mail, email, pop-ups, banner and/or other online advertisements.  

**Navigational Information** : Information about what visitors or customers do online and where they go, including but not limited to recency of visit to specific online areas, frequency of visit to specific online areas, and pathing information.  

**Need to Access** : The need to have access to information, including private customer information, for the fulfillment of an official corporate duty.  

**Notice** : Indications to visitors and customers about policies and practices in effect.  

**Personal Information** : Individual information about a customer that is specific to that customer. Personal information includes but is not limited to anything collected about a customer on an individual level and any information volunteered by the customer, such as a personal profile or preferences.  

**Registration Information** : Customer created, personalized information used to customize services and content, and/or to fulfill transactions.  

**Private Communications** : Communications that are intended to be contained among a defined set of participants, such as e-mail. Message board postings and public room conversations are not considered private communications.  

**Private Information** : Private information includes all information about a customer that the customer has not made publicly available.  

**Public Information** : Public information includes all online information about a customer that a customer has made publicly available.  

**Publicly Available Consumer Data** : Information acquired from consumer marketing and reporting organizations and other publicly available sources.  

**Transactional Information** : Purchase information, including but not limited to date of purchase, source of purchase, recency of purchase, frequency of purchase, dollar amount of purchase, type of product or product category purchased, means of purchase, type of credit card used, other uses of online commerce.   

**Use** : Processing, transmitting, transforming, or otherwise handling information. Includes promotional, advertising, and marketing use.  

**Visitor**: A Visitor to our Web site. Visitors are different from Customers.   
(All Customers are Visitors, but not all Visitors are Customers.)  

**Update Information:**

When we did it: 2 October 2001

What we did: Updated this Privacy Policies page

Why we did it: To include updated, clarifying information about our Privacy Policies, specifically as they relate to disclosure of information to third parties in the process of fulfilling COD orders.
